Guide to the Harry Adams Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Unidentified Subjects, 1951–1985
  - Unidentified Subjects with Dates
    - Exterior portrait of a clown during a parade, 1977 April (Box 13, Folder 674)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and a man, 1977 May (Box 13, Folder 675)
    - Interior portrait of five men, 1977 July (Box 13, Folder 676)
    - Interior views of men and women at an event in a church, 1977 September; 4 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 677)
    - Interior portrait of two women with three men wearing traditional African clothing, 1977 November (Box 13, Folder 678)
    - Exterior view of a seated crowd, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 679)
    - Interior portrait of five women and two men filling glasses from a champagne fountain, probably at a wedding, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 680)
    - Interior portrait of nine women, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 681)
    - Interior view of attendees of a business holidays party, probably at a travel agency, 1977 December (Box 13, Folder 682)
    - Interior portrait of a woman and two men at a New Year's Eve party, 1978 January 1 (Box 13, Folder 683)
    - Overview of tables and attendees at a banquet, 1978 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 684)
    - Exterior portrait of an orchestra with eighteen members, 1980 January 27 (Box 13, Folder 685)
    - View of a group of people near turnstiles, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 686)
    - Interior portrait of a man at a podium, 1981 November (Box 13, Folder 687)
    - Interior portrait of a woman, 1982 February (Box 13, Folder 688)
    - Exterior view of a woman entering a limousine accompanied by a male chauffeur, 1982 October (Box 13, Folder 689)
    - Interior portrait of a woman holding an award of appreciation from Inside Travel News to Harry Adams for his photography, 1982 November (Box 13, Folder 690)
    - Interior portrait of a girl and a woman, 1983 March (Box 13, Folder 691)
    - Interior portrait of a woman with two quilts, 1983 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 692)
    - Interior portrait of three women and two men, displaying a copy of "Africa," by Samuel Okungu, 1983 August (Box 13, Folder 693)
    - Interior portrait of a boy and a priest, 1983 December (Box 13, Folder 694)
    - Interior portrait of three women and three men, 1983 December (Box 13, Folder 695)
    - Interior view of a table with four women and three men at a banquet, 1983 December (Box 13, Folder 696)
    - Interior view of a woman and three men, probably at a meeting of travel agents, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 697)
    - Interior portrait of six men, 1985 February (Box 13, Folder 698)
    - Interior portrait of four women, possibly during a beauty pageant, 1985 April (Box 13, Folder 699)
    - Views and portraits related to a conference of travel agents in Nairobi, Kenya, 1985 May; 28 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 700)
    - View of a headquarters for the Republican Party, probably in Los Angeles, 1985 June (Box 13, Folder 701)
    - Exterior view of two men on the roof of a house, one man operating a hose, probably during a fire, 1985 July (Box 13, Folder 702)
    - Interior portrait of four women and two men, 1985 July (Box 13, Folder 703)
    - Interior portrait of two women and four men, 1985 July; 2 photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 704)
  - Unidentified Subjects without Dates
    This subseries consists of photographic material created by Harry Adams with unidentified subjects an no dates.
    Subseries arranged under four headings: Women, Men, Women and Men, and Views.
    - Women
      - Studio portraits of one woman, 8 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 705-711)
      - Interior portraits of one woman, 21 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 712-732)
      - Interior portraits of two women, 8 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 733-740)
      - Interior portraits of three women, 6 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 741-746)
      - Interior portraits of four women, 3 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 747-749)
      - Interior portraits of five women, 3 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 750-752)
      - Interior portraits of six women, 5 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 753-757)
      - Interior portrait of seven women (Box 14, Folder 758)
      - Interior portrait of nine women (Box 14, Folder 759)
      - Interior portrait of ten women (Box 14, Folder 760)
      - Interior portrait of fourteen women (Box 14, Folder 761)
      - Interior portrait of a large group of women (Box 14, Folder 762)
      - Exterior portraits of one woman, 3 photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 763-765)
      - Exterior portrait of two women (Box 14, Folder 766)
      - Exterior portrait of three women (Box 14, Folder 767)
    - Men
      - Studio portraits of one man, 10 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 768-775)
      - Interior portraits of one man, 18 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 776-791)
      - Interior portraits of two men, 24 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 792-812)
      - Interior portraits of three men, 9 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 813-820)
      - Interior portraits of four men, 2 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 821-822)
      - Interior portrait of five men (Box 15, Folder 823)
      - Interior portrait of ten men (Box 15, Folder 824)
      - Interior portrait of eleven men (Box 15, Folder 825)
      - Interior portraits of large groups of men, 3 photographic prints (Box 15, Folder 826-828)
      - Exterior portraits of one man, 3 photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 829-831)
      - Exterior portraits of two men, 8 photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 832-837)
      - Exterior portraits of three men, 7 photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 838-843)
      - Exterior portrait of four men (Box 16, Folder 844)
      - Exterior portraits of five men, 4 photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 845-847)
      - Exterior portrait of six men (Box 16, Folder 848)
      - Exterior portrait of seven men (Box 16, Folder 849)
      - Exterior portrait of ten men (Box 16, Folder 850)
    - Women and Men
      - Interior portraits of one woman and one man, 35 photographic prints (Box 17, Folder 851-884)
      - Interior portraits of one woman and two men, 18 photographic prints (Box 17, Folder 885-899)
      - Interior portraits of one woman and three men, 6 photographic prints (Box 17, Folder 900-905)
      - Interior portraits of one woman and four men, 4 photographic prints (Box 17, Folder 906)
        Also includes a portrait with another woman and three men
      - Interior portrait of one woman and six men (Box 17, Folder 907)
      - Interior portraits of two women and one man, 18 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 908-923)
      - Interior portraits of two women and two men, 10 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 924-931)
      - Interior portraits of two women and three men, 3 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 932-934)
      - Interior portraits of two women and four men, 3 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 935-936)
      - Interior portraits of two women and ten men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 937)
      - Interior portraits of three women and one man, 3 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 938-939)
      - Interior portraits of three women and two men, 6 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 940-943)
      - Interior portraits of three women and three men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 944-945)
      - Interior portrait of three women and five men (Box 18, Folder 946)
      - Interior portraits of four women and one man, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 947-948)
      - Interior portraits of four women and two men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 949-950)
      - Interior portrait of four women and five men (Box 18, Folder 951)
      - Interior portraits of five women and one man, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 952-953)
      - Interior portraits of five women and three men (Box 18, Folder 954)
      - Interior portrait of six women and three men (Box 18, Folder 955)
      - Interior portraits of six women and four men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 956-957)
      - Interior portrait of seven women and one man, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 958)
      - Interior portrait of eight women and six men (Box 18, Folder 959)
      - Interior portraits of a large groups of women and men, 3 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 960-962)
      - Interior views of banquets, 6 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 963-968)
      - Wedding portraits of a woman and a man, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 969-970)
      - Wedding portraits of five women and a two men (Box 18, Folder 971)
      - Exterior portraits of one woman and one man, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 972-973)
      - Exterior portrait of one woman and two men (Box 18, Folder 974)
      - Exterior portraits of two women and two men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 975-976)
      - Exterior portrait of two women and three men (Box 18, Folder 977)
      - Exterior portrait of five women and four men (Box 18, Folder 978)
      - Exterior portrait of six women and one man (Box 18, Folder 979)
      - Exterior portraits of a large groups of women and men, 2 photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 980-981)
    - Views
      - Golf course (Box 18, Folder 982)
      - Aerial view of a political demonstration (Box 18, Folder 983)
      - Marina with boats (Box 18, Folder 984)
      - Cityscape (Box 18, Folder 985)
      - Church (Box 18, Folder 986)
- Collected Photographs, 1943–1985
  This series consists of photographic material by other photographers collected by Harry Adams, 1943-1985, which chiefly depict Adams with others. Many of the photographic prints have ink stamped dates on versos and occassionally the ink stamps for other photographers.
  Series III is arranged chronologically.
  - Studio portrait of the Nicholas Brothers, Harold Lloyd Nicholas and Fayard Antonio Nicholas, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 987)
  - Studio portrait of Dr. Horse (Al Pittman) and His Musical Jockeys, 1947 January 29 (Box 19, Folder 988)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams wearing a Los Angeles County Guard uniform and speaking on a telephone, circa 1950 (Box 19, Folder 989)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with another man at the Fred Archer School of Photography, 1952 June 4 (Box 19, Folder 990)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams probably in his studio, 1952 December 14 (Box 19, Folder 991)
  - Studio portraits of Harry Adams, 1952; 3 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 992)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams sitting at a table with Henry Armstrong in a restaurant, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 993)
    Inscription by Armstrong on recto
  - Exterior portraits of Harry Adams and others, including Louis Armstrong, at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles, California, during the 9th annual Cavalcade of Jazz, 1953 June 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 994)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams outside his studio at 4223 South Avalon Boulevard, Los Angeles, California, 1953 July 9 (Box 19, Folder 995)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams posed standing by a sign for Irving's Lodge, owned by Irving Rothberg, as well as posters advertising the training of Sugar Ray Robinson, 1954 April 23 (Box 19, Folder 996)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Dorothea Towles at the home of Therese Adams, 1954 May 25 (Box 19, Folder 997)
    Inscription by Towles on Recto
  - Exterior portraits of Harry Adams and others at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles, California, during the 10th annual Cavalcade of Jazz, 1954 June 20 (Box 19, Folder 998)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams in costume with six women and five men, with Adams and three others holding cameras, 1954 November (Box 19, Folder 999)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman holding the bridal bouquet at the wedding reception of Walter M. Woods and Eunice M. Chambers, a daughter of Reverend Timothy Moses Chambers, Sr., 1955 December 14 (Box 19, Folder 1000)
  - Exterior portraits of Harry Adams and a woman at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles, California, probably during an annual Cavalcade of Jazz, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1001)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with two women and six men, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1002)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams posed standing outside his studio, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1003)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams posed squatting with a camera in a street, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1004)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with others, including a woman and a group of four women and a man, circa 1955; 5 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1005)
    Photograph by Your Community Studio
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams smoking a pipe, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1006)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams posed standing with another man with golf clubs and smoking cigars, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1007)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Charles Williams and two women, circa 1955 (Box 19, Folder 1008)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams, 1956 November (Box 19, Folder 1009)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams writing on sheet music, probably at a recording studio, and with a woman, 1956; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1010)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman in front of a barber shop, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 1011)
  - Exterior portraits of Harry Adams with Dinah Washington and Gerald Wilson at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles, California, during the 14th annual Cavalcade of Jazz, 1958 August 3; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1012)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams in a restroom with an attendant identified as William Hoston, 1959 September (Box 19, Folder 1013)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams holding a stuffed dog with a woman, 1959 November 21 (Box 19, Folder 1014)
  - Studio portrait of Leslie Scott with an inscription to Harry Adam, circa 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1015)
  - Interior portrait of Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald) "Pat" Brown with Harry Adams and three other men, 1960 September 16 (Box 19, Folder 1016)
    Photograph by Cliff Hall
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Nat King Cole and two other men, circa 1960; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1017)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with two women, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1018)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with three women and two men at a banquet, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1019)
  - Studio portrait of Harry Adams with four women, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1020)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Sidney Poitier, circa 1960; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1021)
    One print inscribed on recto by Poitier to Adams
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with cameras on tripods, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1022)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman on a beach, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1023)
  - Exterior view of seven male photographers, including Harry Adams, with cameras and a nude model, probably a photography class, circa 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1024)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Kenneth Hahn, 1961 March 4 (Box 19, Folder 1025)
    Photograph by Charles Williams of C. Chuck Williams & Associates
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams at the Los Angeles Sports Arena, 1961 June 18 (Box 19, Folder 1026)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams probably near the intersection of South Central Avenue with East 42nd Street in Los Angeles, California, 1961 November 21 (Box 19, Folder 1027)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman aboard a ship, 1962 July; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1028)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, 1962 November-December (Box 19, Folder 1029)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, probably a debutante, 1963 February 15 (Box 19, Folder 1030)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams using a typewriter, 1963 April (Box 19, Folder 1031)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with another male photographer and another man, probably at a protest against the discriminatory practices by developer Don Wilson at the Southwood Riviera Royale housing tract in Torrance, California, 1963 June; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1032)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams at a meeting of the Los Angeles Board of Education, 1963 June; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1033)
    Photographs by U. S. Bowman
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams at a seashore, 1963 July (Box 19, Folder 1034)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams with Jim Gilliam and others in a locker room for the Los Angeles Dodgers, 1963 September; 3 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1035)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a man, 1963 September; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1036)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams with others, including Al Greene, probably at a party for liquor distributors, 1963 December; 4 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1037)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) Rockefeller as well as a girl and a woman in a wheelchair, 1964 March 13 (Box 19, Folder 1038)
    Photograph by Cliff Hall, includes a press release, probably from the Los Angeles Eagle newspaper
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams, 1964 March (Box 19, Folder 1039)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Arthur Lee Porter, 1964 May; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1040)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams, 1964 May (Box 19, Folder 1041)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with Mervyn Dymally, F. Douglas Ferrell, Gilbert William Lindsay, and another man at Conference of the Unemployed held at Wrigley Field, Los Angeles, California, 1964 May 21 (Box 19, Folder 1042)
  - Exterior view of Harry Adams at Dodger Stadium with Los Angeles Dodgers baseball player Tommy Davis, circa 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1043)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, 1965 September (Box 19, Folder 1044)
  - Exterior view of Harry Adams creating a photograph of five men at a construction site, 1965 November 30 (Box 19, Folder 1045)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, circa 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1046)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams probably at Camp Seely, Crestline, California, 1966 May 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1047)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, 1966 May 15 (Box 19, Folder 1048)
  - Interior portrait of Yvonne Brathwaite (later Burke) with Harry Adams and two women at an election event in Los Angeles, California, 1966 June 12 (Box 19, Folder 1049)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams with a woman and a man, 1967 February 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1050)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with a man and a woman wearing a swimsuit in the background, 1967 June 24 (Box 19, Folder 1051)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams receiving an appreciation award from Sam Yorty, 1968 April 15; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1052)
  - Interior portrait Hubert Humphrey with Harry Adams, 1968 July 28; 4 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1053)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams, 1969 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 1054)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with a boy and a man, 1969 May 18 (Box 19, Folder 1055)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with others at the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Image Awards, 1969 October 11; 5 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1056)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Billy Mills and Buddy Hackett, as well as two other men, probably at a reception and dinner honoring Coretta Scott King at the Cocoanut Grove, a nightclub at the Ambassador Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1969 December 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1057)
    Photograph by U. S. Bowman
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman, circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1058)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with Hank Aaron and Willie Davis at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, 1972 September 7-8 (Box 19, Folder 1059)
    Inscription by Hank Aaron on recto, June 25, 1974
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and Roy Wilkins, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1060)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with another man, 1973 April (Box 19, Folder 1061)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with B. B. King and Gertrude Gipson-Penland, 1974 May 16-17 (Box 19, Folder 1062)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams with others, 1974 December 23; 4 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1063)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams with O. J. Simpson and another man on the sidelines of the Rose Bowl game between Ohio State University and the University of Southern California, 1975 January 1 (Box 19, Folder 1064)
    Photograph by Guy Crowder
  - Interior view of the Echo Barber Shop owned by Harry Adams at the intersection of Central Avenue and 43rd Street, Los Angeles, California, 1975 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 1065)
    Photograph by Murphy Joseph Ruffins, Jr., 1927-2007
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Gilbert William Lindsay and another man, 1975 March (Box 19, Folder 1066)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman at Saint Thomas, United States Virgin Islands, 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 1067)
  - Exterior portrait of Harry Adams at the United States Capitol Building during preparations for the inauguration of Jimmy Carter, 1977 January 21; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1068)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a woman, 1977 March; 2 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1069)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with two women, probably at an event for travel agents, 1978 April (Box 19, Folder 1070)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Gilbert William Lindsay, and Reverend Ike, also known as Frederick J. Eikerenkoetter II, 1978 April (Box 19, Folder 1071)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a man, circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1072)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with a bust of David Ben Gurion by Dorothy Wolf, circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1073)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman, 1981 February 28 (Box 19, Folder 1074)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams with Martin Luther King, Sr., 1981 February (Box 19, Folder 1075)
  - Interior portraits of Harry Adams with others, including Gilbert William Lindsay, when Adams received an award from the City of Los Angeles, 1982 February 5; 5 photographic prints (Box 19, Folder 1076)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and a four men in Nairobi, Kenya, 1985 May (Box 19, Folder 1077)
  - Interior portrait of Harry Adams and a woman, man, and others, circa 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1078)